<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE article PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.1.2//EN" "http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.1.2/docbookx.dtd" [
<!ENTITY legal SYSTEM "legal.xml">
<!ENTITY appversion "0.1">
<!ENTITY manrevision "0.1">
<!ENTITY date "June 2008">
<!ENTITY app "<application>Palimpsest Disk Utility</application>">
<!-- Information about the entities
       The legal.xml file contains legal information, there is no need to edit the file. 
       Use the appversion entity to specify the version of the application.
       Use the manrevision entity to specify the revision number of this manual.
       Use the date entity to specify the release date of this manual.
       Use the app entity to specify the name of the application. -->]>
<article id="index" lang="sl">
  <articleinfo>
    <title>Priročnik <application>Palimpsest diskovnih orodij</application></title>
    <abstract role="description">
      <para>Dokument opisuje program Palimpsest diskovna orodja.</para>
    </abstract>
    <copyright> 
      <year>2008</year> 
      <holder>David Zeuthen</holder> 
    </copyright><copyright><year>2010.</year><holder>Matej Urbančič (mateju@svn.gnome.org)</holder></copyright> 
    <publisher> 
      <publishername>Projekt dokumentacije GNOME</publishername> 
    </publisher> 
      <legalnotice id="legalnotice">
	<para>
	  Permission is granted to copy, distribute and/or modify this
	  document under the terms of the GNU Free Documentation
	  License (GFDL), Version 1.1 or any later version published
	  by the Free Software Foundation with no Invariant Sections,
	  no Front-Cover Texts, and no Back-Cover Texts.  You can find
	  a copy of the GFDL at this <ulink type="help" url="ghelp:fdl">link</ulink> or in the file COPYING-DOCS
	  distributed with this manual.
         </para>
         <para> This manual is part of a collection of GNOME manuals
          distributed under the GFDL.  If you want to distribute this
          manual separately from the collection, you can do so by
          adding a copy of the license to the manual, as described in
          section 6 of the license.
	</para>

	<para>
	  Many of the names used by companies to distinguish their
	  products and services are claimed as trademarks. Where those
	  names appear in any GNOME documentation, and the members of
	  the GNOME Documentation Project are made aware of those
	  trademarks, then the names are in capital letters or initial
	  capital letters.
	</para>

	<para>DOKUMENT IN SPREMENJENE RAZLIČICE TEGA DOKUMENTA SO OBJAVLJENE POD POGOJI PROSTE DOKUMENTACIJE GNU Z RAZUMEVANJEM DA: <orderedlist>
		<listitem>
		  <para>DOCUMENT IS PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" BASIS,
                    WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESSED OR
                    IMPLIED, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, WARRANTIES
                    THAT THE DOCUMENT OR MODIFIED VERSION OF THE
                    DOCUMENT IS FREE OF DEFECTS MERCHANTABLE, FIT FOR
                    A PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR NON-INFRINGING. THE ENTIRE
                    RISK AS TO THE QUALITY, ACCURACY, AND PERFORMANCE
                    OF THE DOCUMENT OR MODIFIED VERSION OF THE
                    DOCUMENT IS WITH YOU. SHOULD ANY DOCUMENT OR
                    MODIFIED VERSION PROVE DEFECTIVE IN ANY RESPECT,
                    YOU (NOT THE INITIAL WRITER, AUTHOR OR ANY
                    CONTRIBUTOR) ASSUME THE COST OF ANY NECESSARY
                    SERVICING, REPAIR OR CORRECTION. THIS DISCLAIMER
                    OF WARRANTY CONSTITUTES AN ESSENTIAL PART OF THIS
                    LICENSE. NO USE OF ANY DOCUMENT OR MODIFIED
                    VERSION OF THE DOCUMENT IS AUTHORIZED HEREUNDER
                    EXCEPT UNDER THIS DISCLAIMER; AND
		  </para>
		</listitem>
		<listitem>
		  <para>UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES AND UNDER NO LEGAL
                       THEORY, WHETHER IN TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE),
                       CONTRACT, OR OTHERWISE, SHALL THE AUTHOR,
                       INITIAL WRITER, ANY CONTRIBUTOR, OR ANY
                       DISTRIBUTOR OF THE DOCUMENT OR MODIFIED VERSION
                       OF THE DOCUMENT, OR ANY SUPPLIER OF ANY OF SUCH
                       PARTIES, BE LIABLE TO ANY PERSON FOR ANY
                       DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, OR
                       CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OF ANY CHARACTER
                       INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DAMAGES FOR LOSS
                       OF GOODWILL, WORK STOPPAGE, COMPUTER FAILURE OR
                       MALFUNCTION, OR ANY AND ALL OTHER DAMAGES OR
                       LOSSES ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO USE OF THE
                       DOCUMENT AND MODIFIED VERSIONS OF THE DOCUMENT,
                       EVEN IF SUCH PARTY SHALL HAVE BEEN INFORMED OF
                       THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.
		  </para>
		</listitem>
	  </orderedlist></para>
  </legalnotice>


    <authorgroup>
      <author role="maintainer">
	<firstname>David</firstname> <surname>Zeuthen</surname>
	<affiliation>
	  <address>
	    <email>davidz@redhat.com</email>
	  </address>
	</affiliation>
      </author>
    </authorgroup>
    <revhistory>
      <revision>
	<revnumber>Priročnik Palimpsest diskovnih orodij V0.1</revnumber>
	<date>2008</date>
	<revdescription>
	  <para role="author">David Zeuthen <email>davidz@redhat.com</email></para>
	</revdescription>
      </revision>
    </revhistory>

    <releaseinfo>Priročnih opisuje različico 0.1 programa Palimpsest diskovna orodja.</releaseinfo> 
      <legalnotice> 
      <title>Odziv</title> 
      <para>To report a bug or make a suggestion regarding the <application>Palimpsest Disk Utility</application> application or
      this manual, follow the directions in the <ulink url="ghelp:gnome-feedback" type="help">GNOME Feedback Page</ulink>. 
      </para>
      </legalnotice>
  </articleinfo>

  <sect1 id="intro">
    <title>Uvod</title>
      <para>This is the <application>Palimpsest Disk Utility</application> user's guide.</para>
    <figure id="mainwindow-fig"> 
	<title>Okno programa <application>Palimpsest diskovnih orodij</application></title> 
	<screenshot> 
	  <mediaobject> 
	    <imageobject><imagedata fileref="figures/main-app.png" format="PNG"/> 
	    </imageobject>
	    
	    <textobject> 
	      <phrase>Pokaže <application>Palimpsest diskovna orodja</application> glavno okno.</phrase> 
	    </textobject> 
	  </mediaobject> 
	</screenshot> 
    </figure>
  </sect1>
 
   <sect1 id="advanced">
      <title>Palimpsest napredna diskovna orodja</title> 
      <para>Palimpsest diskovna orodja so programi z naprednimi zmožnostmi.</para>

   </sect1>

</article>
